

Mobile: 19927537521 Email: scauwang@stu.scau.edu.cn Location: Tianhe District, Guangzhou, Guangdong

PROFILE

I'm familiar to related research areas, thus able to conquer the problems in this filed. Consequently, my positive attitude and strong ability of learning led to my outstanding academic achievement. With a creative and dynamic mind, I'm keen on attending social practice and volunteer work with a quality of hardworking and rigor. I'm always honest by sticking to my promise and always willing to communicate with others or to help them with a great sense of teamwork.

EDUCATION

South China Agricultural University | Computer Technology (Master)

SEP 2018-Now

Major: Artificial Intelligence, Design and Analysis of Algorithms, Data Warehouse and Data Mining, Combinatorial Mathematics, Optimization Theory.

An Hui Jian Zhu University | Internet Of Things (Bachelor)

SEP 2014-JUL 2018

Major: Advanced Mathematics, Circuit and electronic technology, Data structures and algorithms, The computer composition principle, Probability theory and mathematical statistics, Embedded system design, IoT software design basis, Linux programming, Cloud computing and big data, Mass data storage, IoT positioning technology.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

National Innovation and Entrepreneurship Program

MAY 2015-MAY 2016

- As the host responsible for overall project operation, mainly responsible for image recognition.
- Research on fingerprint identification technology in security.

China Service Robot Competition.

MAY 2015

• Mainly responsible for team achievement display, content writing, and project defense.

Anhui province "Internet plus" competition.

June 2016-August 2016

As team leader, responsible for the overall project design, project planning, project operation, and publicity.

National College Students Computer Application Competition

June 2018

• According to the data set of the competition, using machine learning algorithm, data preprocessing, data visualization, feature extraction, parameter adjustment, modeling and evaluation are carried out.

Subproject of National Natural Science Foundation of China

June 2019-Sep 2019

• In order to solve the problem of accuracy of imaging parameters in the field of electron microscopy, we use deep learning technology and convolutional neural network (CNN) with its excellent characteristics of local receptive field, weight sharing and down-sampling.

Skills

Professional Skills:

- Mastering Python programming.
- Expertise in data processing and intelligent decision making.
- Familiar with computer vision
- Grasping data analysis
- Mastering deep learning frameworks (i.e. Tensorflow, MXnet, Pytorch)
- Have a good perspective on emerging technologies (i.e. Self-driving cars)

Language Proficiency:

- Excellent English reading and writing ability, good listening and speaking ability.
- College English Test Band-6 580 points

Honors and Awards

•	University scholarship	every semester
•	Excellent league cadre and outstanding student cadre.	2016.5
•	Social scholarship	2016.5
•	Principal scholarship	2017.6
•	First Class Scholarship (SCAU)	2018.10